# Yair Charit



### Summery:

Currently finishing my B.Sc. at Tel-Hai College, Israel. (Expected Graduation: 03/21) I am a quick and strategic thinker and problem solver.

Great working as part of a team as well as leading it when necessary.

Experienced working and communicating online.

Trained in Bash, C, C++, C#, Java, Assembly, MATLAB, HTML, CSS, Node.js, SQL, JavaScript, Git, Git Bash, Python. (Hands-on courses avg: 92)

## Experience:

**3. 2019 – present:** Assembly and OS Instructor at "Magshimim", Cyber Education Center. Teaching and managing a class, delivering complex ideas in limited time (currently online) 2020-present: freelancer: web design, custom automations, dynamic pages, database set-up and interface, etc.

### Technologies:

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux.

**Programming Languages:** C, C++, C#, Java, Assembly, MATLAB, Bash, HTML, CSS,

Git, Git bash, Python, JavaScript, SQL. Basic knowledge in: Photoshop, IT.

#### **Education:**



2018 – Present: (B.Sc.) Computer Science - Tel-Hai college, Israel.

- Outstanding performance in all programming focus courses.
- Deep understanding of OOP coding and computer's fundamentals (low and high level programming languages).



2012–2016: Highschool education- "Hamoshava", Zichron Ya'aqov.

- 5 units in Computer Science and English
- Excelled in Computer Science.

#### **Qualifications:**



2018: English for Work – The Language Gallery, London

# Languages:

Fluent in Hebrew and English.